on the spot
[Music]
yeah
yeah for me it's it's never boring it's
always fun it's it's changing it's
efficient it is just a good world to be
in it's so fun it's challenging it's
exciting it feels like a hobby but it's
work and I'm happy to go to work every
day why not it feels like like not that
you never do the same thing twice and if
you're doing the same thing twice you're
doing something wrong
so your K is is not fixed that uh you
can start as a consultant but afterwards
you can also grow to another job like
project manager or maybe uh go to a
service desk so it's it's really a
various uh offer and you can grow as
much and as fast as you want what
excites me the most is our customer are
mostly small family companies and they
build their business from the ground and
to understand their business and to be a
part of their success for story that's
really gives me a Sparkle and a drive to
to go on